Guide to the Student Government Association Records RG 5.15
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Student Government Association Records
1940-2003
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. Student Government Association.
RG 5.15
141
21 Linear Feet
The Student Government Association (SGA) is the governing body for the students at Western Connecticut State University. The SGA sponsors numerous academic, recreational, and other student-run clubs and organizations at WCSU. The records include the accumulation of records by successive SGA presidents.
Provenance
Administrative transfer.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The student government has been a part of the university since the 1920s, back when it was the two-year Danbury Normal School. The structure of the student government changed in the 1940s when the DNS changed to the four-year Danbury State Teacher's College. At that time the Cooperative Government Association (CGA) was run by the students in conjunction with the faculty and staff of DSTC. The phylosophy behind the CGA was that the organization benefited the entire school and therefore warranted involvement of all the constituent groups of the DSTC. Students, faculty, and staff all made decisions regarding activities at the college including "Do-Day," the weekend event at the school in which the entire school did activities to help clean and beautify the college.
By the mid 1950s, changes at the college lead to a change in the CGA as well. The college had begun its transition from a teacher's college to a liberal arts college. It was decided that the student government should be run solely by the students and at the start of the 1956-57 academic year, and the CGA changed and officially became known as the Student Government Association.
The Student Government Association (SGA) now serves as the governing body for the students at Western Connecticut State University. The SGA sponsors numerous academic, recreational, and other student-run clubs and organizations at WCSU. Clubs and organizations wishing to receive SGA recognition due so in order to receive funding and other help from the SGA. Clubs seeking funds for activities and events submit their requests to the SGA. The SGA, in turn, will determine whether the request makes sense or not and will then vote on if the club should be granted their request and, if so, should they receive the full amount or a lesser amount.
The students of WCSU run the SGA with members of the university faculty and staff severing as advisors. The organization is comprised of an executive board, senate, and justices. The students of the university elect the members of the executive board to their positions. Elections usually take place in the spring semester for the following academic year. There are four positions that make up the executive board: president, external vice president, internal vice president, and vice president of finance. The president of the SGA leads the SGA and is often the public face of the organization. The external vice president oversees dealings with the various clubs and organization directly. The internal vice president oversees dealings with the Student Senate and other internal factors of the SGA. The vice president of finance has the important job of dealing with all the fiscal matters of the SGA as well as keeping the financial records of all the clubs and organization that the SGA allocates money. The Senate oversees the legislative matters of the organization. The Senate will make motions for bills presented to the Senate, debate the legislation, ask questions of the clubs when needed, and vote on it. Senators can be either elected to their position during the elections or they can be appointed to their role. Justices oversee the legal matters of the SGA and handle all disputes that are brought before them. Their task is to make sure that the rules outlined in the SGA Constitution are met and fulfilled. Like senators, justices too can either be elected or appointed to their positions.
Scope and Content Note
The collection spans from 1940-2003 with the bulk ranging from 1967-present. This collection spans the history of the organization since the time of World War II.
Materials that relate to the founding of the SGA can be found in the first series of the collection which contains the early records. By the mid 1950s when the college was beginning its transition from a teacher's college to a liberal arts college, the cohesiveness between students, faculty and staff began to fade at the school. According to the minutes of the CGA during the spring of 1956, it was agreed that the CGA no longer made sense it the manner it was run and it should be run solely by the students.
The collection contains twenty-one ledger books containing budget reports, student loan records, minutes from SGA meetings, roll book of the SGA members, and phone logs. There are also loose pages from ledger books containing budget records of the SGA clubs and organizations from the 1980s. The collection also contains several photographs of various events, students, faculty/staff/administration, and buildings throughout the history of WCSU.
The focal point of the SGA collection is found in the numerous folders containing various different items from the SGA. Most of the items deal directly with the SGA, but some have a more indirect connection with the organization. Items that directly deal with the SGA include the following: minutes and agendas from SGA meetings, budget reports and club budget requests, records of SGA members during selected years. Also, coverage of some of the SGA elections, SGA activities and programs, letters and other correspondences, student court matters, surveys and evaluations, and other miscellaneous items, are included in this collection. Items indirectly related include the following: minutes from Board of Trustees, Boards of Governors, Student Advisory Board, Student Life Committee, and faculty and University senate meetings. The collection includes promotional material and pamphlets, Student Union/Center matters, budget and tuition information, and external WestConn issues. It also contains WestConn-related clippings from newspapers, primarily the News-Times and The Echo.
Some items of particular interest contained in this collection:
Pub Committee: During the 1970s, a Pub Committee was formed with the goal of establishing a pub/bar on campus. While the records of this committee aren't extensive, they provide some insight to one of the more controversial subjects at the university.
Newsletters: there is a vast collection of newsletters that the SGA subscribed to during the 1980s. These newsletters include Collegiate Headlines, Intercollegiate Press Bulletins, National On-Campus Report, American Student Association, United States Student Association, and Education Update. Most of these publications range from 1981-1990. Some issues are missing but provide a good summary of information about student life at this college and others during this time. There is also a copy of the History of Western Connecticut State College: 75 Years, 1903-1978 by Dr. Charlotte Isham in 1978.
This collection, for the most part, has been arranged in a chronological order. However, starting in 1968, the collection is arranged according to the records of the SGA president during that academic year(s). Individual documents are assigned the date range of the President to whom the records emmanated; however, while some records are dated before or after that tenure they have been left with the records of the president that they were originally associated when processed. The result is that some documents will have one date in their title and another in their date field. Starting with Bruce Giffin, the SGA president during the 1968-69 academic year, all the SGA presidents are listed with the term years they served. It should be noted that in some cases, records that fall under a particular SGA president might not be in the year(s) of his/her term. For instance, Mark Block, SGA president during the 1982-83 academic year, has items contained that came from before he was president. In cases like this, because it dealt directly with the SGA president or something during his/her presidency, it was vital to keep it with that president. Sometimes records cover a time span that does not fall under one presidential term. In case like this, it is filed by the years it covers starting with the first year. The files are arranged under each SGA president with the SGA internal matters at the beginning of it. In most cases, the minutes of the SGA meetings are filed first. There is also a separate box with legal sized folders. Most of these contain SGA legislation bills that span from 1973-1992. They are also arranged chronologically by the SGA president at that time. The photographs were taken for use in the yearbooks and Echo. Effort was made to identify all the images in the photographs. However, this proved to be difficult and while many have been identified, some have not and/or are not complete. Also, due to the difficulty in identifying these images, some may have not been properly identified. Yearbooks and The Echo were used to aid in the identifying process. Copies of The Echo were removed from this collection and are available in Student Publications Collection in the Haas Library Archives and Special Collections.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged chronologically.
The files are grouped into 32 series.
Reports.; Clippings.; Photographs.; Ledgers (account books).; Minutes.; Universities and colleges -- Students.; Universities and colleges.; College students -- Connecticut.; Danbury (Conn.); Correspondence.; Burns, Karen.; Carolan, Paul.; Boskello, Dennis.; Brentari, Janine.; Bellotti, Michael.; Block, Mark.; Bachyrycz, Gary.; Beckett, Elisa.; Lubus, Raymond.; Molito, Justin.; Gomes, Joni.; Kaltschnee, John.; Gill, John.; Gleissner, Ursula.; DaSilva, Joe.; Alhage, Louis.; Adley, Linda.; Saviano, Anthony.; Retalis, Peter.; Snearly, Susy.; Selnick, Laurance.; Mouradian, Andrew.; Moore, Martin.; Pomeroy, Charles.; Pavis, David.; Western Connecticut State University. Student Government Association.; Theriot, Bruce.; Testa, Kristina.; Trotta, Robert.
- Series 1: 1954-1967, 41678
  - Misc. Notes, Jan-Dec 1957, 1954-1958; 41697 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Expenditures, 1958-1961; 41696 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Notes, 1958-1959; 41695 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budgets & Alumni Information, 1958-1965; 41694 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Notes & Minutes, 1961-1963; 41693 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Expenditures, 1961-1968; 41692 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Notes, 1964-65, 1963-1965; 41691 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SGA Budgets & Requests, 1966-1967; 41690 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SGA Minutes, Oct 66- May 67, 1966-1967; 41689 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Attendance & Voting, 1966-67, 1966-1967; 41688 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SGA agendas, Oct 66- April 68, 1966-1968; 41687 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Instruction Manual for Voting, 1966-1970; 41686 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - SGA Minutes, Sept 67- May 68, 1967-1968; 41685 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - SGA Attendance & Voting, 1967-1968; 41684 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budgets & Requests, 1967-1968; 41683 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board of Governors, 1967-1968; 41682 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - SGA Misc., 1967-1968; 41681 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Attendance & Voting, 1968-1969; 41680 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - SGA Misc., 1968-1969; 41679 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Series 2: Karen Burns-SGA President (1969-70), 41671
  - SGA Minutes, April 69- May 70, 1969-1970; 41677 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - College Senate Meetings, June 69- Mar '70, 1969-1970; 41676 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1969-1970; 41675 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
  - Budgets & Requests, 1969-1970; 41674 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - SGA Misc., 1969-1970; 41673 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Club Constitutions, 1969-1982; 41672 (Box 1, Folder 32-36)
- Series 3: Gary Bachyrycz-SGA President (1970-71), 41666
  - SGA Minutes, May 70- April 71, 1970-1971; 41670 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - College Senate Minutes, Jun-70- May-71, 1970-1971; 41669 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondences, 1970-1971; 41668 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1970-1971; 41667 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Series 4: Michael Bellotti-SGA President (1971-72), 41656
  - SGA Minutes, Sept 71- April 72, 1971-1972; 41665 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Requests & Allocations, 1971-1972; 41664 (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
  - College Senate Minutes, Jun-71- May-72, 1971-1972; 41663 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondences, May 71-April 72, 1971-1972; 41662 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Legislation: Higher Education, 1969, 1971-1972; 41661 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Student Loan Applicants, 1972, 1971-1972; 41660 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Power Play, by the CT Citizens Action Group, 1971, 1971-1972; 41659 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - SGA Misc., 1971, 1971-1972; 41658 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - SGA Misc., 1971-1972; 41657 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Series 5: Paul Carolan & Donald Kappel-SGA Presidents (1972-73), 41640
  - SGA Minutes, April 72-April 73, 1972-1973; 41655 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget Reports, 1972-1973; 41654 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Budget Requests, 1972-1973; 41653 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Requests & Allocations, 1972-1973; 41652 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes, Sept 72- May-73, 1972-1973; 41651 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondences, 1972-1973; 41650 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Karen Johnson/Stanley Garrell Correspondence, 1973, 1972-1973; 41649 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - CT Board of Trustees Minutes, 14-Jul-72, 1972-1973; 41648 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CT Board of Trustees Minutes, 8-Sep-72, 1972-1973; 41647 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Student Loan Committee, 1972-1973; 41646 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Judicial Branch: Almonte vs. Fischer, 1973, 1972-1973; 41645 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Why Not Quality? by David Detzer, 1972, 1972-1973; 41644 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SGA Material, 1972-1973; 41643 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - SGA Misc., 1972-1973; 41642 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Budgets & Requests, 1972-1976; 41641 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series 6: Bruce Theriot-SGA President (1973-74), 41627
  - SGA Minutes, May 73-April 74, 1973-1974; 41639 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - SGA Elections & Members, 1973-1974; 41638 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Budgets & Requests, 1973-1974; 41637 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Financial Reports, 1973-1974; 41636 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Expenses, 1973-1974; 41635 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondences, 1973-1974; 41634 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Club Book, 1973-1974; 41633 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student Court, 1974, 1973-1974; 41632 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - WCSC Staff Bulletin, Oct 73- Apr-74, 1973-1974; 41631 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - CT Higher Education Annual Enrollment Survey, 1972 & 1974, 1973-1974; 41630 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CCSC Faculty Evaluations, 1973, 1973-1974; 41629 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - SGA Misc., 1973-1974; 41628 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Series 7: Pub Committee: 1973-1974, 41621
  - Proposals, 1973-79, 1973-1974; 41626 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Members & Reports, 1977-79, 1973-1974; 41625 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Pub Questionnaire Filled Out by Students, 1978, 1973-1974; 41624 (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
  - Pub Questionnaire w/ Results, 1978, 1973-1974; 41623 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Misc., 1973-79, 1973-1974; 41622 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Series 8: Dennis Boskello-SGA President (1974-75), 41601
  - SGA Minutes, April 74- April 75, 1974-1975; 41620 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SGA E-Board Minutes, 1974-1975; 41619 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Budget Requests, 1974-1975; 41618 (Box 2, Folder 39-41)
  - Budget Requests, 1974-1975; 41617 (Box 2, Folder 39-42)
  - Financial Reports, 1974-1975; 41616 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Budget Hearing Notes, 1974-1975; 41615 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Correspondences, 1974-1975; 41614 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Student Court, 1974-1975; 41613 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Student Advisory Board, 1974-1975; 41612 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Varsity Governing Board, April 74- March 75, 1974-1975; 41611 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Standing Conference Committee, 1974-1975; 41610 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Mascot Committee, 1974, 1974-1975; 41609 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Interdorm Committee, 1974-1975; 41608 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Club Book, 1974-1975; 41607 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Speaker's Coordinating Council, 1974-1975; 41606 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - ROTC, 1974-1975; 41605 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Water Board, 1974-1975; 41604 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - SGA Misc., 1974-1975; 41603 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Notes of the Recording Secretary, 1974-1978; 41602 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Series 9: David Pavis-SGA President (1975-77), 41569
  - SGA Minutes, May 75-Dec 76, 1975-1977; 41600 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SGA E'-Board Material, 1976'-77, 1975-1977; 41599 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Budget Requests, 1975-76, 1975-1977; 41598 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Budgets & Expenses, 1975'-77, 1975-1977; 41597 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Club Budget Records, 1975-76, 1975-1977; 41596 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Finance Board Minutes, 1975-76, 1975-1977; 41595 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, 1975-76, 1975-1977; 41594 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Tuition & Fee Info, 1976-77, 1975-1977; 41593 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate Minutes, Oct 75- Feb-76, 1975-1977; 41592 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, 1975, 1975-1977; 41591 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, Sept-Dec 76, 1975-1977; 41590 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, Jan-Feb 77, 1975-1977; 41589 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Board of Trustees, April 77, 1975-1977; 41588 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Board of Trustees, May 77, 1975-1977; 41587 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1977, 1975-1977; 41586 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Seth O.L. Brody Correspondence, 1977, 1975-1977; 41585 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Student Activity Fund Handbook, 1975, 1975-1977; 41584 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Student Advisory Board Resolution From Glenn Manochi, 1977, 1975-1977; 41583 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Higher Education Legislative Report, 1977, 1975-1977; 41582 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Coordinating Council Proposal, 1976, 1975-1977; 41581 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - WXCI/SGA Meeting, Feb 76, 1975-1977; 41580 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Housing, 1976, 1975-1977; 41579 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - N.E.A., 1976-77, 1975-1977; 41578 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Psychology Club, 1975-77, 1975-1977; 41577 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Steve Feldman Reception Invitation, Apr-77, 1975-1977; 41576 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Statement of Student Rights (Draft II), Oct 76, 1975-1977; 41575 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - English Department Case Studies & Writing Lab Annual Report, 1976, 1975-1977; 41574 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Booklet: 8 Basic Facts…, May 76, 1975-1977; 41573 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Academic Calendar, 1976-77, 1975-1977; 41572 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Phone Calls, 1977, 1975-1977; 41571 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - SGA Misc., 1975-77, 1975-1977; 41570 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Series 10: Laurance Selnick-SGA President (1977-78), 41551
  - SGA E-Board, 1977-1978; 41568 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - SGA Clubs, 1977-1978; 41567 (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
  - Club Financial Statements, Sept 77- Apr-78, 1977-1978; 41566 (Box 3, Folder 40-41)
  - Budget Committee, 1977-1978; 41565 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Budget Requests & Notes, 1977-1978; 41564 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Senate, 1977-1978; 41563 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Student Court, 1977-1978; 41562 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Returned Inventory Lists, 1977-1978; 41561 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Returned Petitions, 1977, 1977-1978; 41560 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - New Campus Rally Plans, Oct 77, 1977-1978; 41559 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Letter to Channel 3, 1977-1978; 41558 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Student Employees Booklet, 1977-1978; 41557 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - CT Student Association, 1977-1978; 41556 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Phone Calls, 1977-1978; 41555 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - SGA Misc., 1977-1978; 41554 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - SGA Tutoring Program, 1977-79, 1977-1979; 41553 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
  - WCSC Board of Governors Constitutions, 1977-80, 1977-1980; 41552 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Series 11: Raymond Lubus-SGA President (1978-80), 41507
  - SGA Minutes, April 78-April 79, 1978-1980; 41550 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - SGA Minutes, Oct 79-April 80, 1978-1980; 41549 (Box 3, Folder 58-60)
  - SGA Elections, 1978-79, 1978-1980; 41548 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - SGA Senators Schedules, Fall 1979, 1978-1980; 41547 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - SGA Clubs, 1978-79, 1978-1980; 41546 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
  - SGA Clubs, 1979-80, 1978-1980; 41545 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Budget Committee Report, 1978-79, 1978-1980; 41544 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - SGA Minutes & Budget Requests, 1979-80, 1978-1980; 41543 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Finance Board Min., Feb-April 1979, 1978-1980; 41542 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Finance Board Min., March 79- Apr-80, 1978-1980; 41541 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - SGA Constitution, 1979, 1978-1980; 41540 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SGA Letters, Aug 78-Jan 79, 1978-1980; 41539 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondences, 1978-1980; 41538 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1978, 1978-1980; 41537 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Curriculum Committee Min., June 77-April 78, 1978-1980; 41536 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tutoring Committee, 1977-79, 1978-1980; 41535 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Court, 1979, 1978-1980; 41534 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Varsity Policy Committee, 1979, 1978-1980; 41533 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Pub Committee, 1979, 1978-1980; 41532 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Square Dance Committee, 1979, 1978-1980; 41531 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Parking Regulations Committee, 1979, 1978-1980; 41530 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rules Committee, Sept 78-Feb 79, 1978-1980; 41529 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - I.I.E. Committee, 1980, 1978-1980; 41528 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Budget Rally, 1979, 1978-1980; 41527 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Lobbyist Bill, 1979, 1978-1980; 41526 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - SGA: Photo, Film, TV & Media, 1979-81, 1978-1980; 41525 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Returned Petitions, 1978-1980; 41524 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Board of Governors, March-Nov 1979, 1978-1980; 41523 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Improvement for Instruction & Evaluation, Feb 78-March 79, 1978-1980; 41522 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Statement of Student Rights, 1976, 41521 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Statement of Student Rights, 1976, 41520 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Justification for Low Tuition Rates, Jul-78, 1978; 41519 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Phone Records, Aug 78-May 80, 1978-1980; 41518 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - CT Association for Retarded Citizens, 1978, 1978-1980; 41517 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - National Student Association, 1975-78, 1978-1980; 41516 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - WCSC Special Party Book, 1978, 1978-1980; 41515 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Misc. Blank Forms, 1978-1980; 41514 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, 1978-1980; 41513 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - SGA Misc., 1978-1980; 41512 (Box 4, Folder 41-42)
  - Misc. Correspondences, 1979-1982; 41511 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Club Budgets, 1979-1984; 41510 (Box 4, Folder 44-48)
  - New Student Orientations, 1980-1984; 41509 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Misc., 1980-1988; 41508 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Series 26: Justin Molito-SGA President (1994-95), 41151
    - SGA Min., Aug 94-April 95, 1994-1995; 41178 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
    - SGA Min. (notebook), Sept 94- Aug95, 1994-1995; 41177 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, Sept 94-March 95, 1994-1995; 41176 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Budget Requests, 1994-1995; 41175 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Budget Report, 1994-1995; 41174 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - SGA Clubs Budget information, 1994-1995; 41173 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - SGA Treasurer's Report, 1994-1995; 41172 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Budget Material, 1994-1995; 41171 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Finance Committee, 1994, 1994-1995; 41170 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - SGA Clubs & Organizations, 1995, 1994-1995; 41169 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Bookstore Committee, 1994, 1994-1995; 41168 (Box 12, Folder 26)